hello and welcome to BQ Primo very good
morning to all the viewers overall in
terms of markets clearly a three tenths
of a percent up move is what we are
seeing you have Nifty which is trading
above those 18 600 levels so we're just
around 1.2 percent away from the life
highs as well Bank Nifty is in fact
slightly somber in trade today uh you
know a very flattish move and we've
declined nearly to today's lowest levels
as we speak right now a lot of stock
specific action is what we are
witnessing in trade joining us on the
show to discuss more Israel senior VP
advisory at broking and distribution and
motilal fine
mofsl uh Rahul good morning and welcome
to the show
good morning
now let's start with couple of you know
movers and shakers in trade today you
have a torrent power that is in Focus
they've signed an mou with the
government of Maharashtra a big contract
coming their way with regards to the mou
and the government has said around 71
000 crores is what they are looking to
Garner out of it uh what's your view on
a torrent power specifically from the
renewable space and what would you
advise an investor to do at current
levels
I think uh obviously this is the
positive news for the torrent power and
and if you look at uh entire power
sector as a whole has not done anything
in last six months or maybe a year if
you look at it uh so I think if you if I
look at it uh entire
uh uh if I look at it entire power as a
play and incredible story which has
played out in last uh three four months
then I feel that I think uh there's not
enough room for the power stocks to do
uh two majors in this uh in this sector
uh one is obviously color power and uh
second is Target I think uh both looks
interesting and both have done nothing
in last a few months so I think uh this
was a reward and and what we see from
the lot of uh data points also which
keeps coming that I think the power
consumption has moved up uh in last uh
two months so I feel that I think uh
total power looks interesting resources
are quite favorable from current levels
as well Right Moving on team leads is
another one the stock is up almost three
and a half percent rate an absolute
underperformer if you see the last one
year a 30 to 31 of a downtake is what
we've seen in fact
has upgraded the stock to a buy as well
and clearly uh as you've mentioned you
know a lot of factors that are turning
positive valuations are looking you know
pretty attractive as well uh what is it
that's making you positive on a team
leads
I think one principle thing I think is
stopping as a sector has done nothing as
you rightly pointed out in last one year
and a half and I think valuations have
also cooled off and looking at the green
shoots and what we feel that I think
things are coming back uh overall so
looks interesting to get into this space
uh so now this talk is obviously
underperformed and at reasonable
valuation so I think this is one of the
thing and I think if you look at it the
markets are getting into a broader based
rally they're they're enough uh you know
if you polarized by a large cap stocks
so I think the trigger for that stopping
segment uh we'll figure out it in next
uh one year or so so I think we feel
that our valuation comes what gives us
that one should buy teams for current
levels Right Moving on you have known
life insurance companies that reported
uh numbers as well for the month of May
overall the non-life insurance premium
is grown by almost 18 to 18 031 now if
you look at companies like ICICI Lombard
star health Bajaj New India as well as
it's mainly ICICI Lombard which is
beaten the industry growth number for me
it's grown at 21 whereas the others have
been in that range of three to sixteen
percent uh what's your view specifically
on an ICICI Lombard as well as uh the
non-life insurance sector as a whole
I think uh obviously after a long time
we've seen that uh non-life players have
got into a picture and last a couple of
uh sorry I think last one month or so if
you look at and secondly I think deposit
trigger by that says
the state which we got the news a couple
of weeks back a poster I say cell number
has been in a focus has stopped has been
a Lagarde for quite some time and
obviously there's numbers which has come
up for the month of May uh which is
promising so I feel that the Stock's
valuation is uh promising uh from here
and second obviously
out
life insurance moving on the fmcg back
has been in Focus over the last couple
of trading sessions in fact the fmcg
index itself has already been trading at
li-fi record high levels uh today you
have a Britannia as well as Nestle which
are seeing some smart gains in today's
session uh what's your view on the pack
in both these counters specifically from
evaluation perspective because uh
clearly you know the monsoons are
delayed in terms of the onset in Kerala
uh however you know everyone's now
watching out for how the inflation
number is going to look like what's
going to come out of the MPC tomorrow uh
how are you looking at these do you
think this is just a precursor to what
could be expected
I think the if you look at Q3 numbers
versus Q4 numbers for the most of the
consumer companies I think one uh trend
is very clear I think that the mood of
mood of the consumer has changed and it
has been better than what it was on Q4
secondly let's not forget I think with
the commodity prices have fallen in uh
Q4 and I think that and that's what uh
we've seen the margin expansion in a lot
of uh fmcg companies so my senses I
think uh fmcg are looking at the
consumer boom I think what we are seeing
it and most of the company's post
numbers have validated quite a bit and
has obviously it's reflected in their
country indexes so I feel that uh
obviously stock quite Nestle Britannia
liver medical all of them uh I will be
upgraded I will see some more upside
from here as well looking at it and
secondly whenever we see a foreign
there in their list is obviously at NCG
pack so that's also one of the trigger
for the interesting and going forward I
think as you rightly pointed out that
Monsoon has been uh for a week or so so
I think the most important thing to look
at is I think uh you know the couple of
weeks later how the monster you know
goes and performs or rather than just a
delay or whether there is a You Know
lesson which is good which is going to
be more critical than this so I don't
think so that's going to impact
immediate but I think yes it could
impact more if in case couple of weeks
we'll come to know how the monsoon has
been progressed for me I think as you
rightly pointed out I think uh
tomorrow's NPC's uh meeting will give
better picture on overall inflation
targets and all so I think until now
whatever it's been reported has been uh
better so and that's what we've seen I
think a lot of fmcg stocks they've been
in focus and have done well in last one
month or so right so that's with regards
to fncg players yeah but Tata Motors as
well is in Focus good move seen on that
counter in fact today is investor day
for Tata Motors so I think a lot of
updates that could be coming out of the
investor meets that Tata Motors has as
well uh how are you looking at the
company Rahul
I think uh if I look at Tata Motors as a
whole I think Blockbuster performance of
Q4 I think uh if you look at it after a
long long time Tada motors have
performed in last uh three four months I
think from December onwards we've seen
that monthly numbers have been pretty
strong right now if you look at in Q4
commentary also the Management's
commentary of reducing the debt of jlr
uh you know in a domestic front
passenger plus the commercial vehicle
again coming back into a focus which
will do well and then few Launches on
electric front or also uh would be orbit
very well so I think the good responses
plus the new launches uh of the electric
vehicles uh which is going to be a
better for Tara Motors and thirdly I
think obviously the glr story has been
rolled out globally very well in the
monthly so and GLI numbers also in fact
look at it has been pretty strong so I
think all this puts together I think the
Tata Motors which is underperformed uh
since last uh six eight months have
shown some good strength in post results
as well so I feel that I think there
should be some more upside of 10 from
here uh you know you know before stocks
are just cooling off post later you're
right moving on zomato is an interesting
one to talk about as well I think if I'm
not mistaken
itself has initiated a coverage in the
month of April and that time we had an
upside Target of almost 30 percent at a
price of around 54. uh today if you see
zomato has already breached the Target
price of 70 and it's back at the IPO
price at that range of 72 to 76. a lot
of factors that everyone is watching out
for over there around from you know what
the management has indicated in the
earning it's called plus a lot of
brokerage upgrades post earnings that
have come in as well uh what would your
view be on a Tata motor sorry another
pardon and secondly would we be
revisiting uh an upgrade are you
expecting an upgrade on that front as
well because it's already crossed our
Target price
I think one thing is very clear I think
uh post uh last year of uh fancy and
most of the newest businesses and I
think the valuations have cooled down
for a lot of stocks in that new age
businesses and at some point of time
which became attractive so that is what
uh We've also done for the matter also I
think we picked it at uh initiated a
coverage at right time and stock has
obviously moved from here so I think I
would invade the markets have performed
in the last three months so I believe
that I think one should continue to hold
some ATO uh wait for the q1 numbers and
then we'll take a call I think or
whether to exit or something but I I
just love is acting advise investors to
hold on to Zone
right so that's with regards to where uh
zomato goes overall uh moving from there
on we just have a little more time
what's your view around on a JK Lakshmi
cement because clearly uh with the
acquisition that they've made in the
Eastern region that gives them a better
mix in terms of geography overall uh how
are you looking at the cement pack
because there is some bit of momentum
but very mixed cues is what we are
picking up
I think overall cement as a whole if you
look at it I think uh most of the large
names like ultratech and all they have
been hitting a 52 week high and if you
see in last one year performance of the
most of the cement companies have been
pretty good I think obviously
tremendously to three reasons for it one
is obviously on the Petco prices which
have fallen and I think which is I think
30 and the cement prices are firm and
the volumes are pretty strong and maybe
uh what we see is so I think that
dispatch being based on uh the prices
being formed and and this uh the margin
expansion which will occur well I think
if we talk about I think our post our
budget with a Thrust of spending on
infrastructure which we saw from the
government side and I think which is
quite visible and secondly I think if we
look at uh uh the way the real estate
companies which they came on with their
Q4 numbers and which they give their
updates as well have been pretty strong
and and a lot of companies are one of
the best quarter of their life uh in
this uh this recorder so I think that I
think real estate stocks plus the infra
story plus I think the margin expansions
all to put together are favorable for
the cement companies so I think
obviously uh if I compare between the
a large versus mid-place in a cement
play that I think obviously JK Remains
the top uh top notch in that space I
think there's a huge valuation
difference between them between the are
not select like Ultra attack and uh
ambuja so I think it remains a value
pick uh uh in the cement stage so I
would advise the nurses to buy or hold
on the current levels in J collection
right so JK Lakshmi cement a value pick
coming in from the cement space uh thank
you to all so much for joining us on the
show and sharing my pleasure overall uh
but a good set of mix that we've
discussed in terms of stocks and if you
see in terms of markets they are trying
to make an attempt to inch higher but
how successful they will be is going to
be interesting because two important
events that are lined up with regards to
the MPC as well as the Fed so the
outcome from their own uh whether it's
priced it or not is something we need to
wait and watch that's all that we have
on this segment thanks for watching lots
more lined up on the other side please
stay tuned
[Music]
thank you